Privacy policy

This privacy policy governs your use of the software application Mindpass Password

Management Tool (“Application”) for mobile and desktop devices that was created by

Mindpass Inc. The Application allows users to leverage their spacial memory to keep sensitive

information like passwords secure.

What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?

User Provided Information

The Application obtains the information you provide when you download and register the

Application. Registration with us is optional. However, please keep in mind that you may not

be able to use some or all of the features offered by the Application unless you register with us.

When you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide ( a ) your name,

email address, age, user name, password and other registration information; ( b )

transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or

download or use applications from us; ( c ) information you provide us when you contact us for

help; ( d ) credit card information for purchase and use of the Application; (e) information you

enter into our system when using the Application, such as contact information and project

management information; and (f) data you provide in optional user surveys. We may also use

the information you provided us to contact you from time to time to provide you with

important information, required notices and marketing promotions.

Automatically Collected Information

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but not

limited to, the type of device you use, your devices unique device ID, the IP address of your

device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and

information about the way you use the Application.

Privacy Policy

1

Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?

This Application does not collect precise information about the location of your device.

Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?

Only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us

improve the Application and our service. We will share your information with third parties only

in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; when we

believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the

safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; with our trusted services

providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we

disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement. If

Mindpass Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you

will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in

ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this

information.

What are my opt-out rights?

You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the

Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your

device or via the application marketplace or network.

Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information

We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable

time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 30 days and

thereafter may store it in aggregate. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have

provided via the Application, please contact us at support@mindpass.io and we will respond in

a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in

order for the Application to function properly.

Children

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the

age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with

information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@mindpass.io. We will

delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

Privacy Policy

2

Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide

physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain.

For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who

need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please

be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information we process

and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.

Changes

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any

changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Web site or Application.

You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is

deemed approval of all changes.

Your Consent

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth

in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a

computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not

limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of

which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the United States your

information will be transferred, processed and stored there under United States privacy

standards.

Do we use cookies, pixels, beacons or other tracking technology?

Yes. Such technology enables our systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember

certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process your

transactions. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or

current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use such

technology to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we

can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party

services that track this information on our behalf.

Contact us

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions

about our practices, please contact us via email at support@mindpass.io.

Privacy Policy

3
